Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Transportation
  - Hollywood Burbank Airport (2) (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Includes newspaper clippings & reprints; Agreement between L.A. & Hollywood Burbank Airport re Noise; Friends of Hollywood Burbank newsletter; Folder Burbank Glendale Pasadena Airport; Noise Provision of Federal Grant; news release, proposed Airport Master Plan Update; Hollywood Burbank Airport Master Plan; Origin & Destination Survey
  - Hollywood Burbank Airport (3) (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Letter from Mayor Bradley Opposing Airport Expansion; correspondence re Lockheed Terminal; City Attorney re Recent Events re Airport; Airport Committee List of Members & minutes; Clean Water Grant Program; Housing & Community Development Strategy; Sepulveda Basin Wild; Area Conceptual Revegetation Plan; Financing of Sewerage Facilities Revenue Bond Program
  - Mayor's Hollywood-Burbank Airport Study Committee (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Includes meeting agendas & minutes of Mayor's Study Committee on The Hollywood Burbank Airport; Attorney Letter re KMPC News; City Administrative Officer clippings on Analysis of Proposal Submitted by General Manager of City Dept of Airports; Subcommittee 2 Recommendations, Newspaper reprints; Main Committee List
    Senate Bill: AB 2345 Allowing Revenue Bonds for Hollywood-Burbank Airport
  - Valley-Wide Transportation Council (E-W) (1) (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Includes Council meeting Reminder; Fax from Homeowners of Encino; newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence re State Dept of Transportation; Congestion Management Program; Council meeting minutes; National Highway System Designations & Guidelines; Strategy Options, Shift The Elevated Train Route Back to Burbank Chandler; Council Disappointment Over L.A. County Transportation Commission Plans for Monorail
  - Valley-Wide Transportation Council (E-W) (2) (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Includes Council meeting minutes; newspaper clippings & reprints; Metro Rail clippings on "Life Cycle" Costs of Aerial Versus Subway Technologies; correspondence re Arguments against Monorail; Safety Research; Council Draft news release; Beilenson Letter to L.A. County, Transportation Commission Urging Red Line be Extended to Warner Center; Metro Rail Selection of Alignment; List Supporting Burbank Chandler
  - Burbank Airport (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Contains Memo to Beilenson re Burbank Airport Environmental Noise Pollution & Suggests That Office Help Howard Berman's Staff re Issue
  - Van Nuys Airport& Noise Curfew (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Contains newspaper clippings re Fines & Bans on Pilots & Jets for Violation of Noise Curfew at Van Nuys Airport
  - 1996 Part 150 Steering Committee (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Letter from City Dept of Airports re Susan Little of Beilenson Office Serving on Van Nuys Airport Steering Committee for The Part 150 Noise Compatibility Program, and List of Committee Members; Noise Compatibility Program report
  - Van Nuys Airport Master Plan (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Includes article, "Notes from An Airport Meeting;" correspondence re Environmental Impact Report; Executive Summary, & Draft Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Project notice of Preparation and Initial Study Checklist
  - Constituent Complaints (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Includes Telephone notes & Written & Faxed Complaints re Jet & Helicopter Noise from Aircraft Using Van Nuys Airport
  - Van Nuys Airport (VNY) (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Includes newspaper clippings & reprints; Homeowners Letter to Beilenson re Cost to Federal Government of Van Nuys Airshow; Airport flyer re Aviation Expo '93; Stop The Noise! flyer; Homeowners of Encino newsletter; Board of Commissioners response to Beilenson Letter re Handling of Noise Complaints at Van Nuys Airport
  - Airports National Noise Policy (Box 56, Folder 5)
    City Dept of Airports news release re Reducing Noise; newspaper clippings & reprints; L.A. Dept of Airports Noise Management Bureau Presentation to Van Nuys Airport Citizens Advisory Council; correspondence re Environmental Impact clippings; letters from Congressmen, re Airport Noise; Congressional Record reprints; Van Nuys & Encino Homeowners re National Noise Policy Change
  - Van Nuys Master Plan (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Includes Letter from City Dept of Airports to Beilenson re Master Plan; Homeowners of Encino; Telephone notes; Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study
  - FAA Rule Change Summer 1994 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Includes Beilenson Letter to Federal Aviation Authority re Their Failure to Approve Rule Change requested by Homeowners of Encino re Minimum Safe Altitudes; Homeowners of Encino & Stop The Noise newsletters; Denial of Petition for Rulemaking; Newspaper; clippings & reprints; Cahuenga Pass Property Owners Association request for Raising Minimum Altitude for Helicopters
  - Van Nuys Airport Letters (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Includes Staff Draft & Beilenson; letters & Forms Complaining of Noise Associated with Van Nuys Airport & proposed Expansion
  - Van Nuys Airport (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Includes letters Complaining of proposed Expansion of Van Nuys Airport; Beilenson Reply Stating That The Master Plan Ought to take such Criteria as Environmental, Noise & Economic Factors Into Decision; Congressman Henry Waxman Reply to Gerald Silver; Stop The Noise!; L.A. Dept of Airports Letter to Beilenson re Noise Compatibility Committee; Stop The Noise! newsletters
  - Van Nuys Airport Draft Plan (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Contains City of L.A. Department of Airports Draft Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Requirements Alternatives report February 1996
  - Topanga Canyon Jet Noise FAA (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Correspondence re Gorman Eight Departure Route & Noise; Telephone notes; Letter from Federal Aviation Administration to Beilenson; newspaper clippings & reprints; "Aircraft Noise: Implementation of FAA's Expanded East Coast Plan;" correspondence with Los Angeles Tracon
  - Transportation--General (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence re Application by Ventura County Transportation Commission for Federal Transit Administration (FTA) Discretionary Capital Bus Funding; Metro Transit Engineering Company; Transportation Management Association; Intermodal Surface Transportation Act of 1991; Urban Mass Transit Administration; Valley Rail; Environmental Study re Parkway Calabasas, Route 101
    Assembly Bill: House Resolution 400; report to Accompany H.R. 2890
  - Aircraft Noise FAA West Coast (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Contains two U.S. General Accounting Office Publications: Aircraft Noise: Status and Management of FAA's West Coast Plan, and Aircraft Noise: Eight Airports' Efforts to Mitigate Noise
  - Van Nuys Airport--7/89 Airshow (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Correspondence re Aviation Expo '89 at Van Nuys Airport, Both Supporting Show and Complaining of Noise; newspaper clippings & reprints
  - Issues, Projects (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Includes Handwritten notes re Van Nuys Airport; Federal Aviation Administration Letter to Beilenson re FAA Congressional Congress; Status of Airport Projects and Van Nuys Airport
  - Van Nuys Air Show--July 1991 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence re Severe Noise Disturbance at Van Nuys Airport Air Show from Encino Homeowners, Van Nuys Airport Citizens Advisory Council, Ban Airport Noise, Tazio Properties; Aviation Expo 91 Invitation flyer
  - Aviation Expo '93/'94 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence re Cost to taxpayers of Funding Aviation Expo at Van Nuys Airport; Homeowners of Encino Complaint; Joel Wachs Letter to Beilenson Supporting Show; Aviation Expo 93 Advertising & Media Coverage; Ninety-Nines, Group; Women Pilots Support Show
  - Background (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Handwritten notes re Aviation Noise; Helicopters; Part 150 Plan
  - Board of Airport Commissioners (Box 57, Folder 9)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence from Stop The Noise! Mid-Valley Chamber of Commerce Circular Supporting Van Nuys Airport; Telephone notes; Clippings on Board of Airport Commissioners (BOAC) Meeting; agenda & minutes of Meeting; Survey of Helicopter Activity at Van Nuys Airport; Homeowners of Encino newsletter
  - Burbank Airport (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; correspondence from Citizens for Fair Airport Noise Homeowners Coalition; Burbank Glendale Pasadena Airport; Ban Airport Noise; Environmental Impact Study for Replacement Terminal; Runway Utilization Program Proposed; Beilenson Concerned with Airport Noise; Experience and Excellence: Burbank Glendale Pasadena Airport Authority Annual report 1988
  - Burbank Glendale Pasadena (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Newspaper reprints; Homeowners Associations flyers re Airport; Congressman Howard Berman Letter Concerned with Accuracy of Environmental Impact report re Airport, and His Letter to FAA; Southern California Business Association Letter Urging New Terminals; Homeowner Coalition on Aircraft Noise Call for Congressional Hearing
  - FAA Noise Compatibility Board (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; Van Nuys Airport Citizens Advisory Council agenda; Stop The Noise! Letter to Board, Accusing Them of Failing to Comply with Federal Advisory Committee Act; Telephone notes; Van Nuys Airport Citizens Advisory Council Agenda, Membership List of L.A. Basin Helicopter & Community Compatibility Board
  - Misc. Press (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Newspaper clippings from Daily News and L.A. Times re Mayor Riordan Position on Aircraft Noise, Appointment to Airport Board, Burbank Airport Authority President Defends New Terminal, Palmdale Airport, Valley Airspace Leaves Little Room for Error
  - Van Nuys Airport 12/92 Status (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Includes Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Building on A History of Aviation Excellence April 1995; Information Guide; Status of Van Nuys Airport
  - Helicopter Issues (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Includes Stop The Noise! & Studio City Residents Association Newsletters; newspaper clippings & reprints; Councilmember Laura Chick letters re Low Flying Helicopters; response to Beilenson Letter by Federal Aviation Administration (FAA); Analysis of Helicopter, Activity in Sherman Oaks Area; Telephone notes; Denial of Petition to FAA; Petition for Rulemaking
  - Helicopter Operations (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Ventura Boulevard Council Letter re Van Nuys Helicopter Operations Study & Recommendations; Code of Federal Regulations Aeronautics & Space; Helicopter Noise Mitigation Handbook; Keys to Compatibility (Helicopter); LAX Policy Change Raising Helicopters; Altitudes; Ban Airport Noise newsletter; FAA Letter to Beilenson; Councilwoman Pat Russell Pushing for Federal Policy; Her news release
  - Van Nuys Citizens Advisory Council (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Includes Van Nuys Airport Citizens Advisory Council agendas & Minutes; Telephone notes; Support for Higher Helicopters from Hermosa Beach Resident
  - Van Nuys Master Plan (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Stop The Noise! Homeowners of Encino newsletters; newspaper clippings & reprints; Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Study Workshop Program & Highlights; Fact Sheets; Stakeholder Fax transmittals & Recommendations Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Goals & Policies
  - Van Nuys Airport--City Noise Ordinance (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Stop The Noise! newsletters; newspaper clippings & reprints; Telephone notes; agenda & minutes of City Board of Airport Commissioners; Statement of Howard Berman to L.A Board of Airport Commissioners; Councilman Yaroslavsky Urges Action; Part 150 Noise; Compatibility Study; proposed Noise Ordinance; Encino Homeowners newsletters
  - Van Nuys Noise (Box 58, Folder 10)
    Aircraft & Noise Monitoring & Management System Van Nuys Airport; newspaper clippings & reprints; Stop The Noise! Encino Homeowners newsletters; Draft Ordinance Van Nuys Noise Abatement and Control Regulation
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Telephone notes; Comparison between Part 150 NCP & proposed Noise Regulation at Van Nuys Airport; newspaper clippings & reprints; proposed Noise Regulation; Homeowners of Encino newsletter; agenda & minutes of Board of Airport Commissioners Meeting; Beilenson, Letter to Constituent re Noise; Community Opinion Survey; Beech Aircraft; Survey Results; List of Van Nuys Airport Users
  - Press (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints re Jet & Helicopter Noise & Van Nuys & Burbank Glendale Pasadena Airport
  - Van Nuys Airport--Survey (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; Beilenson letters Responding to Airport Noise Complaints; Congressman Beilenson's Van Nuys Airport Survey--Results; News Release re Results; drafts & Data Tabulation; Staff Memo to Beilenson re Results; Drafts; Survey, Staff Memo to Beilenson re constituents requesting Survey; Staff Memo re Her Participation in Part 150 Noise Compatibility Study
  - Van Nuys Airport-Survey Actual (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Beilenson Letter to constituents re Federally Funded Noise Abatement Study of Van Nuys Airport; Congressman Beilenson's Van Nuys Airport Noise Survey; newspaper clippings & reprints; Staff Memo Summarizing Written Comments & including Some Forms; Beilenson Ne; Release re Results; Staff Note re Part 150 Study Commission; Staff Memo to Beilenson re proposed Survey; Congressman Berman Airport Survey Forms
  - Joyce Emerson Van Nuys Airport (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; Questions to Joyce Emerson re Van Nuys Airport; correspondence re Part 150 Steering Commission; Beilenson Letter to City Dept of Airports Appointing Joyce Emerson to Steering Commission; Commission Program Primer & Study Outline; Aircraft Curfew, Ban Airport Noise newsletters; Federal Aviation Regulations Part 150; Beilenson correspondence with Officials; FAA Presentation to Citizens Advisory Commission
  - Van Nuys Airport--General (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Van Nuys Airport Information Booklet, User Guide; 1988 Noise Complaints Economic Impact Study of LAX, Ontario & Van Nuys Airport; Retlaw Enterprises Development Proposal; Homeowners of Encino, Ban Airport Noise! newsletters; Beilenson Letter to Constituent, Noise Complaint re Study; Aviation Expo '89; Bull Creek Land Use Plans; Citizen Advisory Addresses; Airport Plan & Environs; Newspaper
  - Air National Guard/Anti-SFV Fair Letters (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re Opposition to The San Fernando Valley (SFV) Fair Proposal; correspondence re Support for The Air National Guard in The Sepulveda Basin
  - Rubio Plaza Center--Parking Lot Sepulveda Basin (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Newspaper clippings & reprints; Tenants at Plaza requesting to Park at Encino Little League Field Because Not Enough Parking Available; Shuttle Bus Insufficient
  - R.T.D. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clippings, correspondence, notes re R.T.D. (Rapid Transit District), major Fax transmittals include County Transit Panel Agrees to Cover RTD'S $59 Million Shortfall, Strengthening RTD Stalls
  - Ventura Freeway (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Newspaper clippings, correspondence re Ventura Freeway
  - Rail Construction Corporation (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Fact Sheets, Route maps re Los Angeles Metro Rail Plan, Metro Red Line Project, and Los Angeles County Transportation Commission
  - 3A Robbins Plan (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Newspaper clippings, notes, correspondence, misc. information re 3A Robbins Plan, major Fax transmittals include Funding, Subway-Bus Link, Underground Metro Plan
  - Van Nuys Transit Center (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, newspaper clippings re Van Nuys Transit Center, major include Funding to Support Site Planning, Environmental Analysis
  - Calstart (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Report, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence re Calstart, A California Non-Profit Consortium Developing Advanced Transportation Technologies
  - Calstart (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes, newsletters, newspaper clippings, correspondence re Calstart, A California Non-Profit Consortium Developing Advanced Transportation Technologies
  - Calstart (3) (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Report entitled "Prospects for Alternative Fuel Vehicle Use and Production in Southern California: Environmental Quality and Economic Development"
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Helicopter Operations Study"
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (Box 77, Folder 4)
    Agenda, minutes, report, misc. information re Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study, major Fax transmittals include Noise Compatibility Program and Noise Control
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (1) (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Agenda, minutes, report, meeting notice, misc. information re Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study, major Fax transmittals include Noise Compatibility Program and Noise Control
  - Van Nuys Airport--Part 150 Study Steering Committee Proceedings (2) (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Van Nuys Airport (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Economic Impacts Associated with Implementation of The Touch and Go and All Aircraft Noise Control Curfews"
  - Van Nuys Airport Master Plan (Box 77, Folder 8)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Master Plan Building on A History of Aviation Excellence"
  - Van Nuys Airport/150 Study (Box 77, Folder 9)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study" Background Appendices, Volume one of three
  - Van Nuys Airport/150 Study (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study" Background Appendices, Volume two of three
  - Van Nuys Airport/150 Study (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Report entitled "Van Nuys Airport Part 150 Study" Background Appendices, Volume three of three
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Report entitled "San Fernando Valley East-West Rail Transit Project" Supplemental Evaluation prepared for The Los Angeles County Transportation Commission
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 94, Folder 2)
    Final Environmental Impact report entitled "San Fernando Valley East- West Rail Transit Project" Supplemental Evaluation prepared for The Los Angeles County Transportation Commission
  - Congested Corridor Action Plan (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Report entitled "Congested Corridors Action Plan"
  - Urban Rail Transit Projects (Box 94, Folder 4)
    Report entitled "Urban Rail Transit Projects: Forecast Versus Actual Ridership and Costs"
  - Transp. Policy Strategies (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Report entitled "Moving America, New Directions, New Opportunities, A Statement of National Transportation Policy Strategies for Action"
  - Right-Of-Way Evaluation Project (Box 94, Folder 6)
    Report entitled "Railroad Right-Of-Way Evaluation Project" appendices, prepared by Southern California Association of Governments
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 94, Folder 7)
    Final Subsequent Environmental Impact report entitled "San Fernando Valley East-West Rail Transit Project" Ventura Freeway Advanced Aerial Technology Alternative; including a package re Southern California Regional Rail Authority
  - Electric Trolley Bus Project (Box 95, Folder 1)
    Draft of Environmental Impact report entitled "Electric Trolley Bus Project" Prepared by Southern California Rapid Transit District
  - LACTC (Box 95, Folder 2)
    Information Package containing Fact Sheets, maps re Los Angeles County Transportation Commission (LACTC), major Fax transmittals include San Fernando Valley/North County Mobility Challenges
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 95, Folder 3)
    Reports re San Fernando Valley (SFV) East-West Rail Transit Project, Ventura Freeway Advanced Aerial Technology Alternative
  - State of The Commute (Box 95, Folder 4)
    Executive Summary report re State of The Commute
  - Burbank, Glendale, LA Transit (Box 95, Folder 5)
    Executive Summary report re Burbank, Glendale, Los Angeles Rail Transit Project
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 95, Folder 6)
    Draft of Subsequent Environmental Impact report entitled "San Fernando Valley Rail Transit Project" Ventura Freeway Advanced Aerial Technology Alternative
  - Ventura Improvement Project (Box 95, Folder 7)
    Information Package including Fact Sheets re Ventura Improvement Project (VIP), A brochure included
  - Rail Construction Corporation (Box 95, Folder 8)
    Information Package including Fact Sheets and brochures re Rail Construction Corporation, A Subsidiary of The Los Angeles County Transportation Commission
  - Rail Rapid Transit Project (Box 95, Folder 9)
    Draft report entitled "Los Angeles Rail Rapid Transit Project Metro Rail" Prepared by Southern California Rapid Transit District
  - Right-Of-Way Evaluation Project (Box 96, Folder 1)
    Preliminary Technical report re Railroad Right-Of-Way Evaluation Project
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 96, Folder 2)
    Draft Environmental Impact report entitled "San Fernando Valley (SFV) East-West Rail Transit Project"
  - Bombardier Inc.T Project (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Information Package including correspondence, brochures re Bombardier Inc. Transportation Equipment Group
  - SFV Rail Transit Project (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Report entitled "San Fernando Valley (SFV) East-West Rail Transit Project"
  - SCAG (Box 96, Folder 5)
    Publication by Southern California Association of Governments (SCAG) re Regional Mobility Element, The Long Range Transportation Plan for The SCAG Region
  - LACTC (Box 96, Folder 6)
    Publication by Los Angeles County Transportation Commission (LACTC) re Carpool Lane Plan; an information package re Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority
  - Metropolitan Transportation (Box 96, Folder 7)
    Report by Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation re Study of Restructuring Public Transit Service in The San Fernando Valley; A Publication re Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority
  - Metropolitan Transportation (Box 97, Folder 1)
    Report entitled "A Plan for Los Angeles County Transportation for the 21st Century" by Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority
  - State Scenic Highway Designation (Box 98, Folder 14)
    Contains Los Angeles Times newspaper clippings re Officials in Agoura Hills, Thousand Oaks & Westlake Village suggesting that part of Ventura Freeway be designated a scenic highway, but State Highway Officials disagree
  - Scenic Highway Designation (Box 102, Folder 5)
    Newspaper clippings & Reprint re Calabasas City Council Seeking A State Scenic Highway Designation for 101 Freeway
  - ISTEA TEP Grants (Box 102, Folder 16)
    Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act (ISTEA) of 1991; pamphlet Summarizing Act; Heal The Bay Proposal; Application for L.A. County Transportation Commission Transportation Enhancements Program (TEP); Fax Transmission Sheets
- Veterans
  - GSA: Tree Planting (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, maps re General Services Administration (GSA) Tree Planting
  - Homeless Vets (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, notes, newspaper clippings re Judge Pregerson & Homeless Vietnam Veterans
  - VA Homeless, Salvation Army (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, notes re Judge Pregerson, Joint Venture between VA & Veterans Initiative, Homeless Veterans
  - UCLA Land Use/Deed Change (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, notes, memos re UCLA Land Use, H.R. 2629, Veterans Administration Deed to UCLA
  - VA--Land--Vet Park Preserve (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, notes, memos, newspaper clippings re Veterans Park Preserve Overview, brochure, pamphlet
  - Veterans (Box 123, Folder 6)